接下来我会给你们演示如何在代码里添加断点
I'll show you how we can add breakpoints in our code. Go ahead and
点击屏幕上的bug图标来打开调试器
click on the screen bug icon, to attach the debugger.
打开设置菜单，在SettingsActivity里面我们将会添加两个断点
We'll go to the Settings menu. In the SettingsActivity I'm going to add two
在onPreferenceChange方法里。
breakpoints, in the onPreferenceChange method. I'm going to add a breakpoint at
一个设置在第59行，当是ListPreference并且setSummary被调用时
line 59 in the case of a ListPreference when it's about to set the summary. I'm
另一个断点设置在第63行，当不是ListPreference并且setSummary被调用时
also going to add a breakpoint at line 63, when it's not a ListPreference and it
现在我们运行APP看看 点击Location
sets the summary. Let's go into the app to try it out. Tap on the Location and
然后更改邮编号码。在你点击OK后，断点就会被触发
change the postal code. If you hit OK, then it triggers the breakpoint to
停在这里。这里有此刻这些变量的值
stop at right here. These are the values of the variables at this time.
这里我们能看到新的邮编号码。你可以跳过这个方法，或者进到这个方法里看具体的运行情况。
And we see the new postal code here. You can step over or into the method for
你也可以点击Play来使程序继续运行，或者点击Stop来结束调试
more details. Or you can hit Play to continue. Or Stop to stop the debugger.
我们现在点击Play以便继续。然后我们看到这里被
Let's hit Play to continue. And then we see that the UI has been
更新成一个新的邮编号码了。接下来我们试试
updated to the, the preference summary, is the new postal code. Let's try it for
改变温度单位。点击这里，然后选择英制单位
Temperature Units. You tap here, and then select Imperial.
这会触发ListPreference里的这个断点。点击Play继续
It triggers this breakpoint in the ListPreference case. We hit Play to continue,
现在我们能看到偏好设置里显示的是英制单位了
and then we see that, Imperial is now the preference summary.